Guide to the Group Material Archive 1976-2009 (bulk 1979-1996) MSS.215
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series I: Project Files, 204548
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Source Material] - General AIDS Related Advertisements, 1988-1989; 211051 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Volbild AIDS - Installation Diagrams, December 1988 - February 1989; 211052 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - AIDS It's Big Business poster, [1988-1990]; 211166 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - two New York Times articles blown up, [1988-1990]; 211168 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Subway panels, [1988-1990]; 211167 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - "AIDS - It's Big Business" posters, 1988-1990; 211053 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Defaced subway poster - HIV, [1988-1990]; 211054 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Mathilde Kim - poster, [1988-1990]; 211055 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Advertising Age poster, [1988-1990]; 211165 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Berkeley - "Doug's Exhibition List", 1989; 211056 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - "AIDS deaths" - table, 1989; 211057 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Act Up advertisement, [1989]; 211058 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - New York City Department of Health advertisements, [1989]; 211059 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Rough AIDS Timeline for Artforum, [1989]; 211060 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material], [1989-1990]; 211063 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - "Talk About It" poster, [1989-1990]; 211065 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Three black and white photographs, [1989-1990]; 211066 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Cardinal O'Connor - "Stop this Man", [1989-1990]; 211064 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Artforum - "Seduced and Terrorized", 1989; 211419 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - "Your Message Here" Arlene Crawford's Piece, 1990; 211067 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Source Material] - New York Times Act up advertisement, March 23, 1990; 211068 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Democracy Poll - Newspaper - "Der Tages Spiegel", June 29, 1990; 211069 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Rough timelines, April-June, 1991; 211070 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Whitney Museum Floor plans, April-June, 1991; 211071 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Gran Fury poster, 1990; 211170 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - New York Department of Health poster, undated; 211171 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - New York Department of Health subway panels, undated; 211172 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Know Your Scumbags poster, undated; 211169 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Know Your Scumbags poster, undated; 211173 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - AIDS Subway panels, undated; 211174 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - ["AIDS Timeline" Exhibited Material] - Blown up handwritten letter, undated; 210967 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Artforum International (2 copies), 1990; 211176 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - "Uptown Downtown" Show - newsprint posters and postcards, 1981; 211429 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Mundy McLaughlin, Artwork (4) -"Two Germany's", "Two Japans" + others, 1982; 211430 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - [Hamilton, Joyce with Rollins, Tim] - "She think's she' bad!" - print on newspaper, [1983]; 211431 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Haring, Keith - Fun Gallery, NYC Poster, February 1983; 216169 (Folder 5 Left)
  - "Timeline through America: The Chronicle of US Intervention in Central and Latin America" PS1 Newspaper: "Around 1984: A Look at Art in the 80s", 211432 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Poster for reading room by Bruce Barber, 1984; 211433 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - "Messages to Washington" - Newspapers in exhibition, 1985; 211434 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - "Messages to Washington" - Abortion article in exhibition, 1985; 211435 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - "Messages to Washington" - WPA Calendar, 1986; 211436 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - "Messages to Washington" - Newspapers, 1986; 211437 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - "Democracy Announcement poster, 1988; 211438 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Kruger, Barbara - "The Decade Show" Posters [4], 1989; 216168 (Folder 11)
  - Peace Poster, 1989; 216170 (Folder 10 Right)
  - "Cash Prize" - photocopies of Final Pieces, 1991; 211439 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - "Cash Prize" - Final Pieces in Newspapers - 1 of 2, 1991; 211440 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - "Cash Prize" - Final Pieces in Newspapers - 2 of 2, 1991; 211441 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - "Alternative Space" - Nils Norman, 1991; 211442 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - "Democracy Wall" for Boston - site plans, 1993; 211444 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - "To Die For" Posters [2], c1993; 216167 (Folder 12)
  - CalArts - Group Material Talk at Cafeteria Poster, 1994; 211445 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Sommer Akademie Poster, 1994; 211446 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Art & Intervention Poster, 1995; 211447 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - "Market" - Point of Purchase Floor Plan, Kunstverein München, August 1995; 216155 (Folder 18)
  - "Interplace Access" Poster, Milan, IT, December 1996; 216157 (Folder 16)
  - Candle Sketch Poster, undated; 216158 (Folder 14)
  - Dunkin' Donuts Posters [3], undated; 216165 (Folder 15)
  - Gran Fury - "Good Luck, Miss You", undated; 211448 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Holzer, Jenny - "Inflammatory Essays" print - "36", undated; 211325 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Holzer, Jenny - [Untitled Mounted Print], undated; 216156 (Folder 2)
  - Rollins, Tim, undated; 211321 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Rollins, Tim - "Alienation", undated; 211450 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Spero, Nancy - Antonin Artaud - "Indian Culture" Broadside, undated; 211449 (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Oversize Series II: Correspondence, 204549
  This series contains oversize materials from Series I: Correspondence.
  - Correspondence - floor plan from Jerome Sans (letter), undated; 210966 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Oversize Series III: Press and Promotional Material, 208520
  This series contains oversize materials from Series III: Press and Promotional Material.
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Press - University Art Museum - Pacific Film Archive newspaper, November 1989; 211061 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Press - The Daily Californian, November 10, 1989; 211062 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Press - Cooper Pioneer, April 29, 1982; 211187 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Article- Getting Ready for the Golden Eighties: A Conversation with Chantal Akerman by Gary Indiana, 1983; 211188 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Press - Chicago Catolico, February 1990; 211189 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Press - Oberlin College Observer, October 25, 1990; 211190 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - "Confronting the AIDS Epidemic" - Newspaper, 1990-1991; 211191 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Article from New York Times Magazine - Style by Mary Jo Salter, July 17, 1994; 211192 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Press - "Americana" - Almost Home by Lisa Liebmann, undated; 211193 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Press Art Worker's Coalition articles - Art's magazine, 1970; 211451 (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Oversize Series VI: Photographic Material, 206941
  This series contains oversize materials from Series VI: Photographic Material. This series includes photographs originally exhibited in Group Material projects.
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 1 of 9, 1982; 211177 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 2 of 9, 1982; 211178 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 3 of 9, 1982; 211179 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 4 of 9, 1982; 211180 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 5 of 9, 1982; 211181 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 6 of 9, 1982; 211182 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 7 of 9, 1982; 211183 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 8 of 9, 1982; 211184 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 9 of 9, 1982; 211185 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - "Pity Puppy", 1983; 211420 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - "Democracy Poll" - Black and white prints, 1990; 211186 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Nancy Linn- Matted photograph - 1 of 2, 1993; 211303 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Nancy Linn- Matted photograph - 2 of 2 - inscription to Felix from Julie, 1993; 211304 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Oversize Series X: Objects, 210829
  This series contains oversize materials from Series X: Objects
  - "Market" - [Exhibited Material] - Bunting (flags), 1995; 210841 (Box 53, Object ID: 215.2.0058)
- Accretions 2009: Series XI: "Vital Archive", 210638
  The materials in this series were compiled by Sabrina Locks for her curated exhibition "Vital Archive: Revisiting Group Material's AIDS Timeline," which took place in the Spring of 2009 at the Bard Center for Curatorial Studies. They were added to the collection with the permission of the donor.
  - Vital Archive | Revisiting Group Material's AIDS Timeline Materials, 2009; 204910 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Vital Archive, [2009]; 259987 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Aids Timeline Color Copies-Vital Archive, [2009]; 259988 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Vital Archive, [2009]; 259989 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Vital Archive, [2009]; 259991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Unprocessed Printed Materials and Ephemera, 1970-1990 (Box 63, Box 62, Box 64, Box 65)
- Unprocessed Photos and Emulsion Slides, 1980-1990 (Box 64)